Soule's Dictionary of English Synonyms

Italics, in the printing of a word or a phrase, signify that the expression belongs to a foreign language, and is not yet completely naturalized in English, being still pronounced according to its own tongue.
When a word has more than one signification, the separate groups of synonymes, corresponding to the several meanings, are designated by figures.
Parts of synonymic phrases, enclosed in parentheses, but not italicized, are optional.